Good morning everyone!
Chotto Kisei's early morning is now
starting!
Are you all awake?
I wonder if there are people watching
in the futon right now.
Or on the train.
This is so comfortable.
I love this space.
It's so relaxing.
It's a good morning to stay overnight.
Let's introduce ourselves.
I'm Tsujino Kanami, aka the super-
excited blue Kanamin.
I'm the super-excited pink Haruka, aka
Koizumi Haruka.
I'm the super-excited green Hiyorin,
aka Yoshikawa Hiyori.
We're all blue characters, so please
take care of us.
This program is brought to you by the
students who work hard to promote
something exciting.
The future is promising!
Thank you for watching!
This time, we are going to read the
contents of Julia, Hitoka and Aki's blog
and talk about it.
It's the first time to read a blog.
It's embarrassing.
I don't want to read it.
Let's read it.
I will read Julia's blog.
Julia, September 14th, 2020.
You have been in the business for 11
months.
11 months?
You have been in the business for 11
months since you made your debut today.
You have been in the business for 2
years.
Great!
You have been in the business for 2
years.
By the way, the anniversary of
MondayJr. and 14th is the same day.
It's been a long time since October
14th last year.
What? It's the same day?
I thought it was the first anniversary
since MondayJr.
It's cute.
MondayJr. updates its blog every
Monday, Monday, and Sunday.
I thought it was hot in summer until
recently.
Isn't it cute?
I thought so.
It's cool in the morning and evening
and autumn.
I can sleep without air conditioning.
Air conditioning?
I mean, air conditioner.
I thought it was hot to wear long
sleeves today.
I went to school in the morning and
wore long sleeves because I was in the
school.
It was cold.
What's the content of this?
It's okay.
It was cold to wear long sleeves even
in the school.
I have been eating chestnuts a lot in
the autumn.
I eat chestnut rice or chestnut honey
with ice cream.
I mix it with pancakes and drink Marron
Frappuccino.
I also ate chestnut parfait.
They were all delicious.
Did you eat chestnuts this year?
I ate chestnuts this year.
Congratulations
I haven't watched TV much, so I was
able to join the entertainment world and
of course the idol world without knowing
anything.
I can't believe it will be 2 years next
month.
It was my first time doing everything
twice, every time, and every time.
It was the first time I've had so many
exciting things in a row, and they were
all wonderful experiences.
This summer was special anyway.
The best!
I'm glad I was able to do it.
It was mostly a live broadcast, but I'm
grateful to everyone who supports us.
Thank you so much for always supporting
us.
Please continue to support us.
I'll probably write the same thing next
month.
I think it's similar to what you're
writing.
And this corner is a question from
Julia.
What day is it today?
Today, September 14th, is Men's
Valentine's Day.
What is that? Did you know?
It's a day when men express their love
for women.
In 1991, the Japanese Body Fashion
Association established it.
What?
It's a weird feeling.
October 11th, Tuesday.
It's been a while since we had a live
show.
We'll show you a lot of fun and intense
live performance.
We're waiting for you.
I see.
How about you?
It's too cute.
A man who actively expresses his love
for a woman.
How about you?
It's cute.
Julia will be updated on Monday.
Wednesday is Aki-chan.
Friday is Yori-chan.
It's a great show.
It's already our second anniversary.
It's been a while since we had a live
show.
It's like we've been here the other
day.
Aki-chan came here two days ago.
We didn't talk at first.
But now we're talking a lot.
Julia talks to us a lot.
Please look forward to the next video!
We've really grown up.
Next week, we'll be celebrating our 2nd
anniversary.
Congratulations!
I hope our fans will tweet about it.
I think everyone will tweet about it.
Like, 2 years of ANSAN.
2 years of ANSAN following 1 Day Juria.
Intonation.
I hope you'll do it.
2 years of Juria.
That's good. 2 years of Juria.
It's meaningful.
Let's do it.
And, ZIP HANADA!
We are so grateful to have such a great
audience.
I didn't expect to go home with such a
big audience.
On July 18th, we will hold a concert
there.
We will perform at the venue and we
will go home with a great performance.
I'm so happy.
ZIP HANADA, thank you!
Next, I'm going to read a blog of
Hitoka.
Is it OK? It's about an hour long.
It's a long blog.
It's a blog that says,
I can do anything if I update the blog
of Hitoka on August 28th.
Good evening, I'm Hitoka.
She looks cute.
I feel more united to perform with the
members.
I'm impatient because I can see the
growth of Julia and Aki-chan.
I sometimes call her Sakai.
I'm glad that all the members did a
good job without thinking that it was
hard.
The charm of the super and the rare is
always positive.
And each of them has a great
personality.
It's amazing that each of them has a
great personality and is united to
perform.
I praised myself.
The members and staff of Team Super
Rare are there.
They care about me.
I can do my best.
I can't do what I want, but I hope for
a bright future.
And I hope Team Super Rare will be
fine.
When I entered the venue of Super
Arena, I was worried that I would be too
big and feel small.
I was worried if I could dance well.
I was worried if I could dance well and
perform well.
But I imagined that everyone was in
this venue during the rehearsal.
I thought it would be beautiful if
there was a pen light.
I was a little lonely.
I was worried that I would be lonely,
but I thought I would be able to perform
with everyone someday.
I was excited and I was able to perform
with all my might.
I was thinking about everyone during
the live and performed.
Did I deliver it well?
Which song did you enjoy the most?
I enjoyed the new song very much.
I like the melody and rhythm.
I was singing with the lyrics of the
song.
Please stay with me.
I like the song, but I like the
connection talk.
I was happy to be able to sing the
song.
I want to listen to the song this
season.
I was lonely because I was worried
about how beautiful the venue would be
if it was orange.
I was able to have a new dream.
I sang with a strong feeling that 100%
orange would never come true.
Let's go to Saitama Super Arena
together.
I want to say to the staff and the
public at the live show.
Let's see the beautiful scenery
together.
Each blog is like a letter.
I agree.
It's always hot.
It's like a letter.
How are you?
I like this kind of feeling.
I always talk about it at the live
show.
It's like a report.
I know.
It's like a report, but it's also like
a video.
It's new.
That's great.
As expected of Sakai.
I like the song.
That's good.
There are people who play music every
time.
We have a new song for the song.
It's so comfortable.
Because it's in the next song.
It's cool.
I can hear it.
By adding dance to it,
It's like the next song.
It makes you feel better.
The feeling of going to that song.
It's so cute.
Personally, I really liked it.
I think it's in Sampra.
I was so moved by the sound of the
piano.
When I first heard the music, I was
like,
I was like,
I'll never forget that.
I want to use it again.
Every time the sound source of the
piano changes,
I want to use it again.
Last, I will read the blog posted on
September 16th by Aki-chan.
Good morning, I'm Aki Suda.
Good morning to you early in the
morning.
It's a good timing.
Thank you for your comments and likes
on my blog and Instagram.
I was surprised to find a lot of stalls
that I have never eaten.
I will eat it when I find it again.
I saw it on Instagram.
And, Longhaka...
Longhaka?
I'm reading it normally.
Thank you for answering Longhaka and
Bobhaka's questions.
Thank you for your comments such as, I
like Longhaka and I want to see Aki-
chan's blog.
At this moment, I counted all of
Longhaka's 95 votes.
Bobhaka's 64 votes, Medium's 2 votes,
Half-Twin's 3 votes.
Longhaka has more votes now.
Why did you say Half-Twin when you were
listening to Longhaka and Bobhaka?
It's because of my hair style.
I want you to show your hair style.
We have the result.
Some people said they like both.
Thank you.
Medium's half-Twin's half-Bobhaka.
I had few votes today, but I chose
Bobhaka.
How do you like it?
I'm sorry for making it short.
I feel strange because it's been a
while since I made it short.
I'm lying.
I'm Long.
I'm sorry for lying.
We often say this.
We did it before.
I remember I said, how do you like it?
I'm sorry for lying again.
Thank you for watching our show.
Hoshina-chan was so cute.
Thank you for reading it until the end.
Good luck with your work, school, and
housework.
Don't forget to moisturize your body
and don't forget to eat donuts.
Why?
You're great.
I've never heard of work, school, and
housework.
I think it's new.
Bob?
Have you ever been Bob?
Is Bob here?
Bob is this long.
It's a medium that doesn't reach the
shoulder.
What is this?
Semi-long.
Long.
It's too short.
I'm sorry.
It's still short.
It's shorter than a person.
It's easy to think that I cut it a lot,
but it was cut in a row.
I lost that, so it's short.
It's 5cm.
Really?
It's 5cm square.
I thought I cut it a lot.
But I can see it for a moment.
I can see it.
When I first saw it on the blog, I
thought,
Did you cut it?
I was deceived.
I thought I wasn't told anything.
I thought, Did I talk about that?
My mother was deceived.
Isn't this good?
You're good.
You put seeds on it, didn't you?
On the back.
If Aki-chan becomes Bob, there will be
more people who say Bob is good.
I think so.
I think it's better now.
I think it's better to cut it shorter.
It looks good on you.
I think it's the same with Nao-chan.
Long hair is good, but short hair is
also cute.
Short hair suits people who look good
on it and people who don't.
So I think it's better to cut it
shorter.
I want to cut it a little more.
I've seen it before.
I've never seen a short hair like this.
I want to cut it.
I want to cut it too.
I don't want to cut it anymore.
I want to cut it.
I don't want to cut it now.
Before I cut it, it was this long.
I wanted to cut it.
I cut it twice.
I don't want to cut it anymore.
I want to grow it.
I'm growing it now.
I want to grow it more.
I want to grow it.
At the beginning?
I want to grow it beautifully.
How do you think, MINE?
It's cute.
I know.
I saw it too.
I saw it.
It was cute.
It's really cute.
my neck...
We met at the Stablofest.
Mirei's hair color was so cute.
It was brown and pink.
It was so cute.
I had a chance to talk with Mirei
before going on stage.
We were waiting for the same time.
I said, you are cute.
She said, I'm glad I dyed my hair.
You are always fashionable.
You are cute on Instagram.
I want to be a cute woman.
I admire you.
I saw you on Instagram.
You are Mirei.
I saw you on the debut stage.
You and Piyo were so cute.
I'm glad I dyed my hair.
Mirei was cute when we were recording.
Mirei is cute.
I was able to talk with Mirei for the
first time.
I didn't say it on TV.
When I took a picture with Mirei,
Aki-chan had known Mirei-chan for a
long time.
I told Mirei-chan about it.
And Mirei-chan said,
Ah, I'm happy.
You're cute in that.
But there was an angel.
But we were both nervous at night.
I'm not taking Aki-chan, but...
Are you a parent?
Usually, there are two of us.
I'm the older sister.
Aki-chan's recording is like this.
It's not all of us.
It's the first time we've been close.
I thought I had to be good at reading.
I don't have a sister I can rely on.
It's like Aki-chan.
I was nervous at night.
Aki-chan did her best.
I think it was a good broadcast.
The senior at STA-LAND said,
I want to meet Aki-chan.
I hope I can meet STA-LAND again.
I don't know if it's going to be like
that.
I hope it's calm.
So, I read everyone's blog today.
Each of us had a lot of personality.
You can tell by this, right?
We have been planning for 3 months for
our debut album.
We have an announcement for that.
It will be announced this evening, so
please look forward to it.
Please check out our blog as well.
Please check out our blog.
So, please check out our blog.
We are CHO! Tekimitsu Endeavor.
Have a good day.
I want to be a drama.
We are going to have a project to get
the songs for our debut album.
We are going to get the songs for our
debut album.
We don't charge for the songs.
You can apply for any songs.
We have a prize for the best song.
We are waiting for your application.
Hello everyone. My name is H.Y.P.
I'm Hiyori Yoshikawa Pio.
I'm looking forward to your
application.
Thank you for watching.
I miss you
I'll be waiting forever
You're not coming back here anymore,
are you?
I can say, I can say, I can say it
Stay with me a little bit more
I love you, I love you
Hey, I will never forget
Under the sky where we met
I love you, I love you
I'm happy just to be like this
This kind of time is happiness
A rainbow-colored bench
Will never change
Benji! One, two, six, nine!